Contact

wittyangel_98@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tribörman-05a890a4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Training Management Leadership

Languages

Swedish (Elementary)
English (Professional Working)
Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)
Finnish (Limited Working)

Certifications

SheCodes Basics

Event Success Management Certification

Tri Börman

Technophile | Cosmetologist & Beauty Advisor | Recruiting, Coaching & Training

Finland

Summary

An internationally wide range of experience from hospitality industry to insurance sector in Indonesia and finally to beauty industry In Finland!

A wealth of knowledge and experience gained through roles in both the private and public sectors has allowed me to create an excellent profile to be part of in a busy and challenging environment that is constantly changing.

My expertise including management, compliance, process mapping and improvement, recruiting, coaching, team developing and training. I enjoy being part of a successful and productive team and have the ability to lead, motivate, inspire and develop people at all levels both within the business and with external clients across multi site operations.

Experience

Studio Fancy Cosmetologist & Beauty Advisor June 2018 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Kaarina, Southwest Finland, Finland

Working as an cosmetologist at Studio Fancy

"Bringing Indonesian's hospitality while carrying out procedures to aim the high qualification of Finnish standard"

https://www.studiofancy.fi/

Kimitoöns kommun | Kemiönsaaren kunta | Municipality of Kimitoön Tourism Assistant

January 2015 - June 2015 (6 months)

- Set up and attend exhibitions and holiday shows
- Provide accurate information on things to see and do and where to stay
- Preparing tourist or visitor information

- Producing promotional material and displays
- Making presentations
- Work on product development

Sinarmas MSIG Life AGENCY DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

August 2010 - May 2011 (10 months)

- Collaborate with agency director to enhance their business scale, create & presented strategic business plan
- To conduct training & performance measurement integrating for sales team (sales force level, manager level and agency director level)
- Training, coaching and leadership development

AXA Financial

Trainer for Sales Academy November 2005 - July 2010 (4 years 9 months)

- Responsible for delivering training programs in regular base
- Conduct training how to sell, how to attracted potential customer, how to answered product & service questions from clientS
- Create & presenting product presentations for selling night event, collaborated with sales team to increase the sales
- Manage team development, strategic business plan

MLC Life Insurance Recruitment Manager June 2005 - November 2005 (6 months)

- Recruiting, coaching & team development

RECRUITING:

- Responsible for designing a recruitment process.
- Update recruiting procedures or create new strategies
- Supervise the recruiting team.
- Search for and enforce new sourcing methods to find good candidates.

Novotel Hotels Public Relations Executive October 2004 - March 2005 (6 months)

- part of a pre-opening team of Novotel Hotel & Residence
- monitor public opinion regarding particular issues about hotel

- develop and implement communication strategies & advise management on communication issues and strategies
- plan public relations programmes
- present arguments on behalf of an organisation to government, other organisations and special interest groups
- respond to enquiries from the public, media and other organisations
- arrange interviews with journalists, prepare and distribute media releases, and liaise with and make statements to the media
- write, edit and arrange production of newsletters & in-house magazine
- organise special events such as open days, visits, exhibitions and functions
- plan, develop and manage brand identity
- organise and manage events, exhibitions, conferences and product launches
- procure sponsorship deals.

Education

Turun Ammatti-Instituutti vocational school, Cosmetologist & Beauty Advisor · (February 2019 - November 2021)

Stiepar Yapari Aktripa Hotel Management · (1996 - 2000)